JURAJ GABRIEL

PROFILE

I studied management and economics and until recently worked as branch manager for a car rental company. I have always had a keen interest in technology and computers, so I have decided to change my career path and focus primarily on improving my IT skills full time, studying programing, software development and current trends. I believe my past experiences, strong communication and problem solving abilities together with general knowledge of IT provide good foundations to build upon. My past working experience were focused mainly to management and automotive sector.

EXPERIENCE

BRANCH - FLEET MANAGER, AVIS KOSICE, KOSICE, SR - 2017-2018

- Local AVIS car rental branch with 5 employees and fleet of 50 vehicles.
- Planning, Billing and Reporting
- * B2B & B2C customer care and sales

SERVICE ADVISOR, AZ-SERVIS, BRNO - 2014-2015

- Customer care and sales
- Time-management and scheduling

EDUCATION

NEWTON COLLEGE, BRNO – GLOBAL BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT

BACHELOR DEGREE 2013-2017

SKILLS

- Linguistics fluent in Slovak, English and Czech both written and spoken
- * Experienced with Windows, Mac OS, office suites, GIT, Jira and Confluence
- Knowledge of HTML and CSS
- * Experience in Python, Django and basic JavaScript and React.JS
- Basic knowledge of databases (MySQL, MongoDB), web-applications
- Experience with cloud web-applications (AWS)

REFERENCES

https://github.com/NoSayMe http://superblog2045.ga